var questions = [
    {
    question: "Which of the following statements about JavaScript is FALSE?",
    choices: ["JavaScript is the dominant client-side scripting language of the web", 
    "Brendan Eich created it in 10 days in 1995", 
     "JavaScript and Java are inter-related", 
     "The first browser to run JavaScript was Netscape 2"],
    answer: 2
  },
 {
    question: "Which is NOT a 'recommended practice' when using JavaScript?",
    choices: ["Ending statements with semi-colons", "closing '{' and '(', or braces and parentheses",
    "the use of strict mode ","Always using concat instead of + or +="],
    answer: 3
}, {
    question: "Which function adds an element at the begining of an array?",
    choices:["push()", "pop()", "shift()", "unshift()"],
    answer: 3
}, {
    question: "Which of the following about 'NaN' is FALSE?",
    choices: ["NaN is numeric", "NaN === NaN", "Number.isNaN(NaN)", "NaN is a global property"],
    answer: 1
}, {
    question: "Which is TRUE about 'Math.random()' ?",
    choices: ["It is an object", "It provides cryptographically secure random numbers", "It returns a '1' sometimes",
    "It returns a random number between 0 and 0.9999999"],
    answer: 3
}, {
	question: "When creating names for Variables, which of the following is NOT allowed in JavaScript?",
    choices: ["starting with a letter", "using letters, underscores, and dollarsigns", "using Javascript keywords",
     "choosing case-sensitivity carefully"],
    answer: 2
}, {
	question: "Which symbol meaning is WRONG in JavaScript?",
    choices: ["++ : increment", "=== : equal value and equal type", " % : percentage", 
    "|| : logical or"],
    answer: 2
}, {
	question: "Which is NOT an object?",
    choices: ["undefined","Array", "RegExp", "null"],
    answer: 0
},{
	question: "Which is NOT a type of loop used in JavaScript?",
    choices: ["for", "for/in", "while", "for/ a while"],
    answer: 3
},{
	question: "What will the code below output to the console? console.log(1 +  +'2' + '2');",
    choices: ["32", "122", "14","5"],
    answer: 0
}
];